I see you crying on the bed The poison he put in
your head He made you feel so small and cheap A
promise that he couldn't keep But then I see you
look at him Our Jordan on a sudden whim He holds
you And you're finally safe He's the antidote,
he's the escape I see the way that Marty smiles I
see the way that Zoe stares We all can see his
kindness And how much he truly cares The old
world rules would make us fight Would make us
choose and turn away But I have something
different I have something new to say Why must
love be a competition? A single prize, a selfish
war It's not a game of possession It's something
so much more I don't feel any jealousy I only feel
what's true If he's the one who's healing you
Then he belongs to you too We're a different kind
of constellation A new design, a brand new light
No jealousy, just care Tonight
you're hurting and you need someone who's good
and kind and clean he's sitting right beside you
he is right here i have a massive crush on him i'll
say it it's okay but it doesn't make me angry To
see you feel this way I see the way that Muddy
smiles I see the way that Zoe stares We all can see
his kindness And how much he truly cares The old
world rules would make us fight But I am not
afraid of this new loving system that we have
made Why must love be a competition? A single
prize? A selfish war? It's not a game of
possession It's something so much more I don't
feel any jealousy I only feel what's true If he's
the one who's healing you Then he belongs to you
too We're a different kind of constellation A
new design, a brand new light No jealousy Just
care Tonight
No, just see Just care tonight